all right hostas welcome back and in this tutorial I'm going to show you guys
好的东道主欢迎回来 本教程我将向你们展示
how to use bitwise operators in Python now just the heads-up it's probably
如何 在Python中 使用 按位运算符 现在只是 单挑， 它可能
really useful if you guys already know binary so if you guys don't then go ahead and watch my networking tutorials
如果你们已经知道，真的很有用 二进制所以如果你们不这样做的话 提前看我的网络教程
one of the videos in there I explained how to interpret binary basically if you
我解释过其中一个视频 如果你基本上 如何解释二进制
have a value like 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 then how to turn this value into an actual number if you can do that then you're
有一个像1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1那样的值 如何将此值转换为实际值 数字， 如果你能做到那么你就是
ready to watch this video and if not then I'll talk you guys through real
准备观看此 视频，如果没有 然后我会通过真实的方式与你们交谈
quick but you know just the heads up so let's say that we have two different values so we'll say we have a value a
很快， 但你知道只是抬头 让我们说我们有两个不同 因此我们会说我们有一个价值 a
and this is just equal to the regular number 50 no binary or anything like
而这 仅仅等于常规 50号没有二进制 或类似的东西
that and we have another number B and this is equal to 25 well if you guys
那我们 还有另一个号码 B和 如果你们 这个，这 相当于 25
remember the binary of 50 let's see if I can get it it's a what is it 1 1 0 0 1 0
记得50的二进制文件让我看看 可以得到它它是什么它1 1 0 0 1 0
I think that's it art so the binary of the value 50 is 1 1 0 0 1 0 now of
我认为这是艺术所以二进制 现在的值50是1 1 0 0 1 0
course this place is for the ones this is for the 2 4 8 16 and 32
当然这个地方是为了 这个 是2 4 8 16和32
all right that's interesting but what do we care well if we try to end it with the value of 25 which is let's see 0 1 1
好吧那很有意思 但是做什么 如果我们试着用它来结束它，我们会很好 25的值是让我们看到0 1 1
0 0 1 alright check it out so adding these together in normal human language
0 0 1好吧 检查出来这样添加 这些在正常的 人类语言中
would just give you 75 right well whenever you do a binary and you don't
只会给你75分 每当你做一个二进制文件 而 你没有
add them together in that kind of way so whenever you have a binary and what
以这种方式将它们组合在一起 每当你有二进制和什么
you're going to do is use the ampersand operator so a and B so let me give
你要做的就是使用＆符号 操作员所以A和B所以让我给
myself some more space
我自己多了一些 空间
all right so what the binary and does remember is it goes through and it puts
好吧那么二进制和做什么 记住，它是通过它，它 放
a zero unless the top in the bottom are both ones so if one of these is a zero
零，除非底部的顶部是 两者都是如此，如果其中一个 是零
or both of them is zero then it gets a zero so zero for this one since this one
或两者都为零然后得到一个 因为 这个，所以这个零为零
is a zero and one for this one basically the only time you're going to get one is
基本上 是一个零 和一个 你唯一一次得到一个是
when both of them are ones so this one's a zero this one's definitely a zero this
当他们俩都是这样 的时候 零这个肯定 是零
one 0 and this one zero so that's what it does it goes through and it adds them
一个0 和这一个 零，这就是什么 它经历了它并添加它们
together in other words it finds a result and it only has a 1 when both of those are ones so now what we can do is
换句话说，它找到了一个 结果， 两者都只有1 那些是现在我们能做的就是
we can print C and whenever we do that it will give you 16 so we can verify
我们可以打印C 和每当我们这样做 它会给你16，所以我们可以验证
that by making sure so 1 2 4 8 16 and no 32 so that is indeed correct that's
通过确保如此1 2 4 8 16 和没有 32这样确实是 正确 的
what's going on now let me copy this right there and all right so the next
现在发生了什么让我复制这个 就在那里，好吧，所以下一个
thing I want to teach you guys is right shift and by the way there's also or and
我想 教 你们的 事情 是 对的 转移，顺便说一下，还有和
you know a bunch of other stuff but I figured if you guys know how to do and
除了我，你还知道其他一些东西 如果你们知道该怎么做想通和
then you guys don't have to do or now one kind of tricky thing is binary right shift and I'll give you guys an
那么你们不必做或现在 一种棘手的事情是二元权利 转移，我会给你们一个
explanation of what the heck this is so say that you have variable and it's just equal to human readable 240 that's just
解释这 是 怎么回事 说你有变数而且只是 等于人类可读240就是这样
the value and 240 in binary is 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 so what we want to do is we actually want to take 240 and right
二进制的值和240 是1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0所以我们想做的就是我们 实际上想要拿240和右
shift it that means take all these bits is shift them to the right now whenever
转移它意味着采取所有这些位 现在每当他们转移到右边
you do that the bits on your left are just going to turn to 0 so what we're
你这样做左边的位是 我要改为0
basically doing is this we're going to make a new variable called Y and this is going to be equal to X
基本上这样做是 我们要去的 创建一个名为Y的新变量，这 是 将等于X.
with every bit shifted two spots to the right now if you ever want to do left
每一位都移动了两个点到 现在，如果你 想做左派
then just use less than less than but let's take this and shift every bit two
然后使用少于 但 不到 让我们把它转移到每一位
spots to the right so instead of 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 we get 0 0 remember the first
右边的 点， 而不是1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0我们得到0 0 记住 第一个
one ROV zeros 1 1 1 1 0 0 so now you can see that we're pretty much is taking
一个 ROV零1 1 1 1 0 0 所以现在你可以 看到我们正在接受
these bits and shifting them to the right 2 spots so now what we can do is
这些位并将它们转移到 正好 2点， 所以现在我们能做的就是
you can actually print Y and check it out so the original value was 240
你可以实际打印Y 并检查它 因此原来的价值是240
however the value of 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 that is indeed 60 and if you want to run that through some online calculator then
但值为0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 这确实是60，如果你想跑 那通过一些在线计算器然后
you can validate that but trust me guys it is I wouldn't lie to you actually I
你可以验证，但相信我们 实际上，我 不会骗 你
would but but not about this alright so there you go that is how you do binary
但会但未谈及这个这么 好吗 你去的那就是 你做 二进制的方式
and in binary shift uh yeah that's all I got to say alright see you guys next
二进制 转移呃是的，这就是我 得说说好的， 接下来 你们
time
时间